Guide to the Dial/Scofield Thayer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Scofield Thayer Correspondence, 1879-1931; Series IV; 8.75; (19 boxes)
  - Blayney, Lindsay, 1924
  - Block, Alexander, 1924
  - Bodenheim, Maxwell, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 743)
  - Booth, Edward T., 1923-25 (Box 28, Folder 744)
  - Bourne, Randolph, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 745)
  - Braithwaite, William Stanley, 1926
  - Brandenburg, Margaret, 1924-25 (Box 28, Folder 746)
  - Brentano's, 1924
  - Brevard, Lee, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 747)
  - Brewer, Joseph, 1922
  - British Museum, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 748)
  - Britten, Clarence, 1918-20
  - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1921
  - Brown, William Slater, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 749)
  - Bryant, Louise, 1920-23 (Box 28, Folder 750-51)
  - Buermeyer, Lawrence, 1923-24 (Box 28, Folder 752)
  - Burke, Kenneth, 1921-23 Apr (Box 28, Folder 753-762)
  - Burke, Kenneth, 1923-28, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 763-67)
  - Burroughs, Bryson, 1922-23 (Box 29, Folder 768)
  - Bynner, Witter, 1920
  - "C" general, 1907-25 (Box 29, Folder 769-70)
  - Calverton, V. F., 1924-25 (Box 29, Folder 771)
  - Carter, E. Scofield, 1914-15
  - Cary, Alita, n.d.
  - Chace, Dr. Arthur F., 1924 (Box 29, Folder 772)
  - Chagall, Marc, [1923?] (Box 29, Folder 773)
  - Chapman, Josephine, 1923
  - Charles and Co., 1924
  - Churgel, Lillian F., 1924
  - Clark, Dr. L. Pierce, 1921-26 (Box 29, Folder 774)
  - Coatsworth, Elizabeth, 1923-24 (Box 29, Folder 775)
  - Coggeshall, Thomas, 1916
  - Colum, Padraic, 1921-22
  - Cournos, John, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 776)
  - Cowley, Malcolm, 1921-24, n.d.
  - Craig, Gordon, 1923
  - Craig, S. W., 1921-23 (Box 30, Folder 777-80)
  - Craven, Thomas, 1921-24 (Box 30, Folder 781)
  - Crompton, M. V., 1927 (Box 30, Folder 781a)
  - Cummings, E. E., 1913-25, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 782-94)
  - "D" general, 1921-26 (Box 30, Folder 795)
  - Damon, S. Foster, 1923-25 (Box 30, Folder 796)
  - Dehn, Adolf, 1922-26 (Box 30, Folder 797-98)
  - Demuth, Charles, 1921-24, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 799-801)
  - DePollier, Dorothy Elise, [1925?] (Box 30, Folder 802)
  - Dewey, John, 1918
  - Douglas, Norman, 1922-23 (Box 30, Folder 803)
  - Dow, Joy Wheeler, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 804)
  - Duffus, R. L., 1920 (Box 30, Folder 805)
  - Dyer, Charles, 1916, n.d.
  - "E" general, 1921-23 (Box 30, Folder 806)
  - Edwards, Walter A., 1907, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 807)
  - Eliot, T. S., 1915-25 (Box 31, Folder 808-11)
  - Eliot, Vivien, 1915-21 (Box 31, Folder 812-13)
  - Erdberg, Amy von, 1922-31 (Box 31, Folder 814-15)
  - Erdberg, Robert von, 1910-23 (Box 31, Folder 816-38)
  - Erdberg, Robert von, 1924-28, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 839-41)
  - Erdberg, Robert von: Summaries of his letters, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 842)
  - d'Estray, Jean, 1916-21, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 843)
  - Evans, Harold, 1920-21 (Box 32, Folder 844)
  - Eveline, Mrs. H. B., 1924 (Box 32, Folder 845)
  - "F" general, 1920-25, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 846)
  - Faggi, Alfeo, 1921-24 (Box 32, Folder 847)
  - Farrar, Mary, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 848)
  - Farrar, Reginald, 1916
  - Farrar, Valentine, 1914-15 Oct, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 849-56)
  - Flechtheim, Alfred, 1921-24 (Box 32, Folder 857-58)
  - Frank, Waldo, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 859)
  - Freud, Sigmund, 1921-25, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 860)
  - Fry, Roger, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 861)
  - "G" general, 1918-24 (Box 32, Folder 862)
  - Galantière, Lewis, 1919, 1924-25 (Box 32, Folder 863-64)
  - Galerie Simon, 1923-25 (Box 32, Folder 865)
  - Gallatin, A. E., 1924
  - Gerash, Alfred, 1921-23 (Box 32, Folder 866)
  - Gerstley, Henry, 1924
  - Gor'kiï, Maksim, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 867)
  - Gourmont, Rémy de, 1920
  - Gregory, Alyse, 1920-34, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 868-90)
  - Grisogono, Marietta de, 1923-26 (Box 33, Folder 891-95)
  - Guillaume, Paul, 1923-24 (Box 33, Folder 896)
  - "H" general, 1920-29, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 897-900)
  - H.D. (Box 34, Folder 901)
  - Hallowell, Robert, 1920-26 (Box 34, Folder 902)
  - Hardy, Thomas, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 903)
  - Harris, Frank, 1920
  - Hartley, Marsden, 1922, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 904)
  - Harwood, H. Cecil, 1915-20 (Box 34, Folder 905)
  - Henniker-Heaton, Raymond, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 906)
  - Herreshoff Manufacturing Co., 1924-25
  - Hesse, Hermann, 1922-23 (Box 34, Folder 907)
  - Hillyer, Robert, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 908)
  - Hoeffert, W. H., 1921-22 (Box 34, Folder 909)
  - Hofmannsthal, Hugo von, 1922-25 (Box 34, Folder 910-12)
  - Holloway, Emory, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 913)
  - Huebsch, B. W., 1919-25 (Box 34, Folder 914)
  - Hughes, Ernest, 1924-25 (Box 34, Folder 915)
  - "I" general, 1921, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 916)
  - "J" general, 1921-25 (Box 34, Folder 917)
  - Jaeger's Sanitary Woolen System, Inc., 1924 (Box 34, Folder 918)
  - Jayson, Alice, 1922-23 (Box 34, Folder 919)
  - Johnson, Carl, 1925
  - Johnson, Martyn, 1918-20 (Box 34, Folder 920-24)
  - Johnson, Richard, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 925)
  - Johnston, William, 1924
  - Joyce, James, 1919-20 (Box 34, Folder 926)
  - Jurié, Erik von, 1925-26 (Box 34, Folder 927)
  - Jury, C. R., 1914, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 928)
  - "K" general, 1907-25 (Box 34, Folder 929-31)
  - Keer Maurer Co., 1923-25 (Box 34, Folder 932)
  - Kent, Henry W., 1923-24 (Box 34, Folder 933)
  - Kimball, Mrs. Everett, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 934)
  - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1921-24 (Box 34, Folder 935-36)
  - "L" general, 1918-25 (Box 34, Folder 937)
  - Lachaise, Gaston, 1919-25 (Box 34, Folder 939-40)
  - Laurencin, Marie, [1924?] (Box 34, Folder 941)
  - Lauriat, Charles E., Jr., 1919-25
  - Lawrence, D. H., 1920-21 (Box 34, Folder 942)
  - Leaverton, Ernest, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 943)
  - Leonard, Jonathan, 1924
  - Lepsius, Reinhold, 1914, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 944)
  - Leslie, Shane, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 945)
  - Lewandowski, Leon, 1924
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 946)
  - Lowell, Amy, 1920-23 (Box 34, Folder 947)
  - Loy, Mina, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 948)
  - "M" general, 1915-25 (Box 34, Folder 949-50)
  - McBride, Henry, 1920, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 951)
  - MacCarthy, Desmond, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 952)
  - McMillan, E. A., 1924, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 953)
  - MacVeagh, Lincoln, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 954-55)
  - Mahler, Alma, 1918, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 956)
  - Malkiel, Henrietta, 1922-23 (Box 35, Folder 957)
  - Mann, Heinrich, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 958)
  - Mann, Thomas, 1921-24 (Box 35, Folder 959-60)
  - Marconnier, Byrne, 1923-25 (Box 35, Folder 961)
  - Meier-Graefe, Julius, 1922-25 (Box 35, Folder 962-67)
  - Mencken, H. L., 1921-24 (Box 35, Folder 968)
  - Mills, Martha Chalmers, 1923-24 (Box 35, Folder 969)
  - Mitchell, R. Stewart, 1921-25 (Box 35, Folder 970)
  - Moholy-Nagy, L., 1922-23 (Box 35, Folder 971)
  - Moll, Carl, 1922
  - Moore, George, 1921-23 (Box 35, Folder 972)
  - Moore, Marianne, 1920-29 (Box 35, Folder 973-84)
  - Moore, Mary Warner, 1925-26 (Box 36, Folder 985)
  - Mortimer, Raymond, 1915-25, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 986-1002)
  - Muir, Edwin, 1921-25 (Box 36, Folder 1003-04)
  - Munro, Kathryn, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 1005)
  - Murry, J. Middleton, 1924
  - "N" general, 1923-24 (Box 36, Folder 1006)
  - New Gallery, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 1007)
  - Nichols, R. T., 1911-17 (Box 36, Folder 1008-11)
  - Nichols, R. T., 1918-27, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1012-22)
  - North, Ernest Dressel, 1924-25 (Box 37, Folder 1023)
  - Norton, Lucretia, 1923-24 (Box 37, Folder 1024)
  - Nuggatt, Dudley, 1916-17 (Box 37, Folder 1025)
  - "O" general, 1916-25 (Box 37, Folder 1026)
  - Onderdonk, Andrew, 1915-26 (Box 37, Folder 1027)
  - Orr, Alexis, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1028)
  - Orr, Elaine, 1921-26, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1029-33)
  - Ortner, Ella, 1923-24 (Box 37, Folder 1034)
  - "P" general, 1920-25, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1035-36)
  - P., R. Q., 1923-25 (Box 37, Folder 1037)
  - Panagopoulos, P., 1920
  - Parker, Eleanor, 1924-25 (Box 37, Folder 1038)
  - Parker, Kathryn, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 1039)
  - Parr, Robert, 1914-18 (Box 37, Folder 1040-41)
  - Perkins, Harley, 1924-25 (Box 37, Folder 1042)
  - Phillips, Cecil, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 1043)
  - Phillpotts, Eden, 1923-24
  - Piel, Paul, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 1044)
  - Plimpton, Russell, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 1045)
  - Plumb, William W., 1920
  - Pound, Ezra, 1915-23, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1046-74)
  - Pound, Homer, 1920-21 (Box 38, Folder 1075)
  - Powys, Llewellyn, 1923-25, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1076-78)
  - Powys, Philippa, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 1079)
  - Quinn, John, 1920-24 (Box 38, Folder 1080)
  - "R" general, 1907-24 (Box 38, Folder 1081)
  - Rascoe, Burton, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 1082)
  - Regli, Warren, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 1083)
  - Revillon Frères, 1924-25 (Box 38, Folder 1084)
  - Rhinelander, Philip, 1911 (Box 38, Folder 1085)
  - Riccius, Hermann P., 1918-22 (Box 38, Folder 1086-88)
  - Riccius, Hermann P., 1923-25 (Box 39, Folder 1089-95)
  - Robinson, Boardman, 1923-25 (Box 39, Folder 1096)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1921-23 (Box 39, Folder 1097)
  - Rogers, Burke, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 1098)
  - Rönnebeck, A., 1921-22
  - Rosenberg, Paul, 1923-24
  - Rosenfeld, Paul, 1919-21 (Box 39, Folder 1099)
  - Rosenshine, Annette, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 1100)
  - Ruff, Gisela, 1923-26, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1101-03)
  - Rumsey, Mary H., 1921-24 (Box 39, Folder 1104)
  - "S" general, 1921-26, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1105-06)
  - Sachs, Paul J., 1924-25 (Box 39, Folder 1107)
  - Santayana, George, 1913-24 (Box 39, Folder 1108-09)
  - Saun, Leslie P., 1924 (Box 39, Folder 1110)
  - Schermerhorn, Eleanor, 1921-25 (Box 39, Folder 1111)
  - Scheuermann, Frank, 1924-25
    See also: Box 67, folder 1784
  - Schnitzler, Arthur, 1921-25 (Box 39, Folder 1112-13)
  - Schultz, Harleigh B., 1924-25 (Box 39, Folder 1114)
  - Scofield, Mrs. J. M., 1909-15 (Box 39, Folder 1115)
  - Scofield, Myrtis (Mrs. William), 1924-26 (Box 39, Folder 1116)
  - Scofield, William B., Jr., 1900-26 (Box 39, Folder 1117)
  - Scott, Evelyn, 1919-20, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1118)
  - Seeger, Alan, 1914-16, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1119)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1915-1922 Aug (Box 40, Folder 1120-51)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1922-25, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1152-71)
  - Simonson, Lee, 1920-21, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1172)
  - Societé Anonyme, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 1173)
  - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1924-27 (Box 41, Folder 1174)
  - Stearns, Harold, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 1175)
  - Stein, Leo, 1924-25 (Box 41, Folder 1176-77)
  - Stephens, James, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 1178)
  - Stern, Josef, 1924
  - Stevens, Wallace, 1923
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 1179)
  - "T" general, 1921-26 (Box 41, Folder 1180)
  - Thayer, Ellen, 1915-26, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1181-84)
  - Thayer, Ernest, 1905-21 (Box 41, Folder 1185)
  - Thayer, Florence, 1907-18 May (Box 42, Folder 1186-1211)
  - Thayer, Florence, 1918 Jun-1924 (Box 43, Folder 1212-36)
  - Thayer, Florence, 1925-31, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1237-45)
  - Thayer, Josephine, 1915 May 23 (Box 44, Folder 1245a)
  - Thayer, Lucy, 1914, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 1246)
  - Thayer, Mary P., 1923-24 (Box 44, Folder 1247)
  - Theis, Otto F., 1924 (Box 44, Folder 1248)
  - "U-V" general, 1919-25, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1249)
  - "W" general, 1907-26 (Box 44, Folder 1250-51)
  - Wadley and Smythe, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 1252)
  - Wadsworth, P. Beaumont, 1922-24
  - Ware-Pratt Co., 1924 (Box 44, Folder 1253)
  - Warren, Herbert P., 1915
  - Washington Square Association, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 1254)
  - Watson, Hildegarde Lasell, 1912-26 (Box 44, Folder 1255)
  - Watson, James Sibley, Jr., 1920-26, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1256-64)
  - Wescott, Glenway, 1923-24 (Box 44, Folder 1265)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1920-26 (Box 44, Folder 1265a)
  - Wilson, Andrew, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 1266)
  - Wilson, Arthur, 1921
  - Wilson, [James], 1921
  - Wilson, Stella, 1921
  - Wittenberg, Sophia, 1920-25 (Box 44, Folder 1267-68)
  - Wright, Cuthbert, 1913-26, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1269-80)
  - "Y" general, 1921-24 (Box 45, Folder 1281)
  - Yeats, William Butler, 1923-24, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1282)
  - "Z" general, 1922-24 (Box 45, Folder 1283)
  - Ziegler, Marie, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 1284)
  - Zweig, Stefan, 1922-23, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1285)
  - Unidentified, 1905-26, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1286-97)
  - Third Party Correspondence
    - Avis, M., 1909 (Box 45, Folder 1298)
    - Bullock, Mabel, n.d.
    - Clarke, Courtlandt C., 1914, n.d.
    - Duchêne, J., 1915 (Box 45, Folder 1299)
    - Gardner, L. M. D., n.d.
    - Kennicott, E. P., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1300)
    - Miller, Mamie E., 1913
    - Nickerson, Hoffman, 1915
    - Orr, Elaine, 1916-22
    - Osler, Sir William, 1914 (Box 46, Folder 1301)
    - Potter, Emma, n.d.
    - Smith, Nancy Earle, n.d.
    - Thayer, Ed[ward], 1879 (Box 46, Folder 1302)
    - Thayer, Ernest, 1907-24
    - Thayer, Florence, 1913, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1303-04)
    - Thayer, Lucy, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1305)
    - Thayer, Mrs. Schuyler, 1917
    - [Thompson, Eben Francis], 1915, n.d.
  - Unidentified, 1914-22, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1306)
  - Empty Envelopes, 1905-27, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1307-18)
- Personal Papers, 1895-1941; Series V; 11.5; (22 boxes)
  Series V, Personal Papers, is contained in Boxes 47-68
  and is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Address book, [1925?] (Box 47, Folder 1319)
  - Birth certificate, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 1320)
  - Calling cards and address slips (Box 47, Folder 1321)
  - Divorce papers
    - Correspondence with lawyers, 1921-24, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1322)
    - Decree and notification, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 1323)
    - Legal fees for Nancy Thayer adoption, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 1324)
  - Draft papers
    - Draft notices and exemptions, 1917-18 (Box 47, Folder 1325)
    - Identification cards, 1916-17 (Box 47, Folder 1326)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1917-18 (Box 47, Folder 1327)
  - "Dreams: Clark": manuscripts and typescripts, 1925, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1328-30)
  - Financial papers: Bills and receipts
    - "A" general, 1913-26, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1331-32)
    - "B" general, 1914-26, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1333-34)
    - Dr. H. V. Barclay, 1920, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 1335)
    - The Benedick, 1915-25 (Box 47, Folder 1336)
    - Clarence O. Bigelow, Inc., 1918-24, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1337-38)
    - Birrell and Garnett, 1926, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1339)
    - The Blackstone, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 1340)
    - J. H. Block Co., 1915-21 (Box 47, Folder 1341)
    - Borden's Farm Products, 1918-25 (Box 47, Folder 1342)
    - Hotel Brevoort, 1916-25, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1343-47)
    - Hotel Bristol, 1925, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1348)
    - Brooks Brothers, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 1349)
    - Burns Brothers Coal, 1918-25 (Box 47, Folder 1350)
    - "C" general, 1914-25, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1351-53)
    - Charles and Co., 1924 (Box 48, Folder 1354)
    - E. Chervet et fils, 1921-23 (Box 48, Folder 1355)
    - Dr. L. Pierce Clark, 1919-21 (Box 48, Folder 1356)
    - Consolidated Gas, 1918-25 (Box 48, Folder 1357)
    - Copley Plaza, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1358)
    - "D" general, 1914-26, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1359-60)
    - Dial, 1916-25, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1361)
    - Dreicer et Co., 1916-25 (Box 48, Folder 1362)
    - Louis G. Dreyfus, 1916-17 (Box 48, Folder 1363)
    - L. A. Dubernet, 1914-24 (Box 48, Folder 1364)
    - F. L. Durne and Co., 1915-16 (Box 48, Folder 1365)
    - "E" general, 1913-25 (Box 48, Folder 1366)
    - Edgartown Drug Store, 1917-24 (Box 48, Folder 1367)
    - El Camino Real Motor Car Co., 1916-17 (Box 48, Folder 1368)
    - Hotel Esplanade, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1369)
    - Excelsior, 1920-25, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1370)
    - "F" general, 1918-24, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1371-72)
    - "G" general, 1914-26, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1373-74)
    - "H" general, 1914-24, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1375)
    - Haas Pharmacy, 1920-21 (Box 48, Folder 1376)
    - Harbor View Hotel, 1917-18 (Box 48, Folder 1377)
    - Harrold's Motor Car Co., 1918-20, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1378)
    - Harvard Club, 1916-24, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1379)
    - Harvard Endowment Fund, 1919-23 (Box 48, Folder 1380)
    - "I" general, 1918-25 (Box 48, Folder 1381)
    - "J" general, 1915-19 (Box 48, Folder 1382)
    - "K" general, 1917-25 (Box 48, Folder 1383)
    - Kent-Costikyan Rugs, 1918-23 (Box 48, Folder 1384)
    - Knapp-Ritzmer Co., 1920-25 (Box 48, Folder 1385)
    - J. N. Knight and Son, 1918-22 (Box 48, Folder 1386)
    - "L" general, 1917-24 (Box 48, Folder 1387)
    - Lai-Yuan Co., 1918 (Box 48, Folder 1388)
    - Charles E. Lauriat Co., 1915-19 (Box 49, Folder 1389-91)
    - Lewandes, 1918-21 (Box 49, Folder 1392)
    - "M" general, 1914-25, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1393-94)
    - W. A. McLaughlin, 1916-24 (Box 49, Folder 1395)
    - Magdalen College, 1914-15 (Box 49, Folder 1396)
    - James Martin Co., 1919-21 (Box 49, Folder 1397)
    - Elkin Mathews, 1915-16 (Box 49, Folder 1398)
    - Metropolitan Storage Warehouse Co., 1916-18 (Box 49, Folder 1399)
    - A. Mistel and Son, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 1400)
    - Muriel Murray, 1916, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 1401)
    - "N" general, 1915-26 (Box 49, Folder 1402)
    - New England Telephone and Telegraph, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 1403)
    - New York Edison Co., 1915-25 (Box 49, Folder 1404)
    - New York Telephone Co., 1917-25 (Box 49, Folder 1405)
    - Newcome's Detective Bureau, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 1406)
    - Ernest Dressel North, 1919-25 (Box 49, Folder 1407)
    - "O" general, 1915-25 (Box 49, Folder 1408)
    - "P" general, 1917-24 (Box 49, Folder 1409)
    - Hotel Pennsylvania, 1925 (Box 49, Folder 1410)
    - Potter Stables, 1917-18 (Box 49, Folder 1411)
    - "Q" general, 1915-18 (Box 49, Folder 1412)
    - "R" general, 1915-25, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1413-14)
    - Revillon Frères, 1917-23 (Box 49, Folder 1415)
    - James Roddy, 1915-17 (Box 49, Folder 1416)
    - "S" general, 1915-25, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1417-20)
    - Santa Barbara Gas and Electric Co., 1916-17 (Box 49, Folder 1421)
    - Santa Barbara Transfer Co., 1916-17 (Box 49, Folder 1422)
    - Dr. Harold Steinberg, 1918-19 (Box 49, Folder 1423)
    - Dr. Josef Stern, 1921-23 (Box 49, Folder 1424)
    - "T" general, 1915-26, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1425)
    - Tiffany and Co., 1916-23 (Box 49, Folder 1426)
    - "U" general, 1916, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1427)
    - "V" general, 1917-24 (Box 50, Folder 1428)
    - Dr. Agnes Vietor, 1919-20 (Box 50, Folder 1429)
    - "W" general, 1915-25 (Box 50, Folder 1430-31)
    - Wadley and Smythe Florists, 1918-25 (Box 50, Folder 1432-33)
    - John Wanamaker Co., 1915-24, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1434-35)
    - Washington Square Garage, 1916-25 (Box 50, Folder 1436-37)
    - Western Union, 1916-17, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1438)
    - Wiener Bank, 1923, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1439)
    - Andrew Wilson, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1440)
    - Worcester Club, 1915-25 (Box 50, Folder 1441)
    - "Y-Z" general, 1914-25, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1442)
  - Financial papers
    - Contracts, 1915, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1443-44)
    - Expense Accounts
      - Thomas Malone, 1920-25, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1445-52)
      - Eleanor Parker, [1921-25] (Box 50, Folder 1453)
      - Unidentified, 1923-24 (Box 50, Folder 1454-55)
    - Fifth Avenue Bank: statements, 1923-25 (Box 50, Folder 1456)
    - Income tax law, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1457)
    - Insurance policy, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 1458)
    - Leases and estimates
      - "80 Washington Square East", 1916-19, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1459-62)
      - See also: Oversize, Box 74, folder 1947
      - "Santa Barbara house", 1916-17 (Box 50, Folder 1463-64)
      - "Vienna apartment", 1922 (Box 50, Folder 1465)
    - Promissory notes, 1914-24 (Box 51, Folder 1466)
    - Thayer estate: charter for yacht, 1905 (Box 51, Folder 1467)
    - Thayer estate: legal correspondence, 1938-41
    - Trust agreement: William B. Scofield, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 1468)
    - Trust agreement: Nancy Thayer Cummings, 1925-40 (Box 51, Folder 1469)
  - Genealogical information, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1470)
  - Greeting cards, 1903-26, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1471-72)
  - Inventories, 1938, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1473)
  - Inventories of books, 1911-21, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1474-77)
  - Invitations, 1916-17, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1478)
  - Letters of introduction, 1921-22 (Box 51, Folder 1479-80)
  - Medical information
    - Diet lists, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1481)
    - Memoranda and prescriptions, 1919-23, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1482-83)
    - Water purity analyses, 1924-25 (Box 51, Folder 1484)
  - Memorabilia
    - Address book, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1485)
    - Billfold and contents (Box 51, Folder 1486)
    - Blackboard, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1487)
    - Comb (Box 51, Folder 1488)
    - Lavender sachet sent by Marianne Moore (Box 51, Folder 1489)
    - Painting on board, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1490)
    - Pen (Box 52, Folder 1491)
    - Stamps, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1492)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1917-22, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1493-94)
  - Notebooks, 1909-21 (Box 52, Folder 1495-1505)
  - Notepads, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1506-09)
  - Notes and memoranda (Box 54, Folder 1510)
  - Notes and memoranda (Box 55, Folder 1511)
  - Notes and memoranda (Box 56, Folder 1512)
  - Notes and memoranda (Box 57, Folder 1513-15)
  - Notes on vocabulary, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1516-18)
  - Passports, 1915-31 (Box 57, Folder 1519-20)
  - Photographs
    - Persons
      - Cummings, E. E., n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1521)
      - Douglas, Norman, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 1522)
      - "H. R. C.", 1913 (Box 57, Folder 1523)
      - Harvard Monthly editors See: Oversize, Box 74, folder 1948
      - Knauth, Arnold Whitman, 1906 (Box 57, Folder 1524)
      - Morris, Victor, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1525)
      - Mortimer, Raymond (Box 57, Folder 1526)
      - Eliot, Vivienne, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1527-28)
      - Schnitzler, Arthur, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1529)
      - Thayer, Florence and Thayer, Scofield, [ca. 1890] (Box 57, Folder 1530)
      - Thayer, Scofield, 1903-12, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1531-33)
      - Whidden, Austin C., n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1534)
      - Unidentified men, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1535-41)
      - See also: Oversize, Box 74, folders 1949-51
      - Unidentified women, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1542-45)
      - See also: Oversize, Box 74, folder 1952
      - Unidentified groups, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1546-47)
    - Other photographs
      - "Automobiles", n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1548)
      - "Old photos-private", n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1549)
      - "Photos taken by Watson of eclipse", n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1550)
      - Publicity stills: Old Spain, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1551)
      - [Thayer yacht?], n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1552)
      - Unidentified scenes, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1553)
  - Postcards
    - Cards from albums, 1906-16, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1554-63)
    - Miscellaneous cards, 1909-22, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1564-66)
  - Printed material
    - Advertisements, 1918-23, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1567-70)
    - Art: exhibition notices, 1924-27, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1571)
    - Art: miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1572)
    - Handbill on General Strike of Paper Box Makers Union
      See: Oversize, Box 74, folder 1953
    - Magazine: Drawing and Design, 1924 (Box 58, Folder 1573-74)
    - Newspaper clippings
      - Arbuckle case, 1921 (Box 58, Folder 1575)
      - Divorce cases, 1921
      - Dial, 1925-29, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1576)
      - Douglas, Norman, 1918 (Box 58, Folder 1577)
      - Ellerman-McAlmon marriage, 1921 (Box 58, Folder 1578)
      - Keyserling, Eduard von, 1915-21 (Box 58, Folder 1579)
      - Mother Goose controversy, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 1580)
      - Obituaries, 1916-24, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1581-82)
      - Olympic games, 1924 (Box 58, Folder 1583)
      - Poetry, 1920, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1584)
      - Reviews, 1922-28, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1585)
      - Rex v. Rothwell case, 1924 (Box 58, Folder 1586)
      - Thayer family, 1907-24 (Box 58, Folder 1587)
      - Theater, 1923-27, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1588)
      - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1589)
    - Pamphlets